Like a murder
像谋杀一样
Wow
哇
Ok
好
On
上
Common
共同
So I have to like my something to
所以我必须喜欢我的东西
Ok so
好吧
Anyone know if this is that heavy
任何人都知道这是否很重
Yeah I don't feel like I should have gone in the charts now
是的，我不认为我现在应该进入图表
Ok
好
Can I have the harder you work on way from yourself going
我能不能让您在前进的路上更加努力
Slightly down
稍微下降
Just need to get the string bags
只需要拿绳子袋
It's not my
不是我的
Sharpening a knife I would use this tool here to send interpreting stand for in straightening the blade
磨刀我将在这里使用此工具来发送解释架以拉直刀片
Techniques my preferred one is to put the honing Steel straight down against the board that allows me to make sure that I
我最喜欢的技术是将珩磨钢笔垂直向下放在板上，这样我就可以确保我
Right angle
直角
I'm sure you can find the blade up here
我确定你可以在这里找到刀片
Working camels
工作骆驼
I find this nothing to be less accurate I find this more conducive for accidents so down or is better in the latest
我发现这没什么不准确，我发现这更有利于意外事故的发生，或者在最近的情况下更好
On the board instead of a house
在木板上而不是房子上